// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
        answer: "background-color",
        options: [
            "bgcolor",
            "color",
            "background-color",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The property in CSS used to change the text color of an element is -",
        answer: "color",
        options: [
            "bgcolor",
            "color",
            "background-color",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
        answer: "font-size",
        options: [
            "text-style",
            "text-size",
            "font-size",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is -",
        answer: "style",
        options: [
            "style",
            "styles",
            "class",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The HTML attribute used to define the internal stylesheet is -",
        answer: "<style>",
        options: [
            "<style>",
            "style",
            "<link>",
            "<script>"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: " Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
        answer: "background-image",
        options: [
            "background-attachment",
            "background-image",
            "background-color",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?",
        answer: "padding",
        options: [
            "padding-left",
            "padding-right",
            "padding",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The CSS property used to make the text bold is -",
        answer: "font-weight : bold",
        options: [
            "font-weight : bold",
            "weight: bold",
            "font: bold",
            "style: bold"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Are the negative values allowed in padding property?",
        answer: "No",
        options: [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "both",
            "May be"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property of margin properties?",
        answer: "margin",
        options: [
            "margin L",
            "margin R",
            "margin",
            "None Of Above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is -",
        answer: "opacity",
        options: [
            "opacity",
            "filter",
            "visibility",
            "overlay"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to specify the space between every letter inside an element?",
        answer: "letter-spacing",
        options: [
            "alpha-spacing",
            "character-spacing",
            "letter-spacing",
            "alphabet-spacing"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: " The CSS property used to specify whether the text is written in the horizontal or vertical direction?",
        answer: "writing-mode",
        options: [
            "writing-mode",
            "text-indent",
            "word-break",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: " How to select the elements with the class name example?",
        answer: ".example",
        options: [
            "example",
            "#example",
            ".example",
            "Class example"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: " The CSS property used to draw a line around the elements outside the border?",
        answer: "outline",
        options: [
            "border",
            "outline",
            "padding",
            "line"
        ]
    },
    // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
    // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    //   {
    //   numb: 6,
    //   question: "Your Question is Here",
    //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
    //   options: [
    //     "Option 1",
    //     "option 2",
    //     "option 3",
    //     "option 4"
    //   ]
    // },
];